你们不会知道洗个澡是多爽的
You have no idea how good it feels to be clean.
你要加力擦洗
You have to work extra hard
才能把蚂蟥的粘液从你指头上洗掉
To scrub leech slime off of your fingers.
欢迎回家 妈妈
Well, welcome home, mom.
当你出门的时候
While you were away,
爸爸干了些很男子汉的事情
Dad did some manly things.
包括升级了你的垃圾粉碎机
Including upgrading your garbage disposal.
- 你是不是把它弄坏了  - 别跑题了
- you broke it, didn't you? - not the point.
皮特 你确定你知道
Pete, are you sure you know how
怎么安装垃圾粉碎机么
To install a garbage disposal?
别跑题了
Not the point.
你应该试试  用的可顺手了
You should try it. it works great.
我们把冰箱里连帕克都不吃的剩菜
We tested it with all the leftovers in the fridge
都拿来做测试了
That we couldn't even get parker to eat.
这就是为什么我对丢进粉碎机
This is why we have strict rules
的剩饭剩菜有严规戒律
About what goes into the disposal.